Guide to the Henry Ernest Sigerist Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1897-(1913-1957)-1970; Series I; 12 linear feet (30 boxes)
  - General, 1947-1957
    - Hanser (Carl) Verlag, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 507)
    - Hardt, Kurt von(*), 1948-1955 (Box 14, Folder 508)
    - Harmel, Merel H., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 508)
    - Hauff, Bruno(*), 1948-1952 (Box 14, Folder 509)
    - Hauff, Bruno(*), 1953-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 510)
    - Hauff, Günther, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 511)
    - Hausmann A. G., 1948-1953 (Box 14, Folder 511)
    - Hazemann, R. H., 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 512)
    - Heaton, Claude E., 1947 (Box 14, Folder 512)
    - Hechr, Celia (Mrs.Se1ig), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 513)
    - Heiman, Jacob, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 513)
    - Hein, Wolfgang-Hagen, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 514)
    - Helfant, Murray H., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 514)
    - Helfgott, Julia Older,(Mrs. Nathan J.), 1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 515)
    - Heller, F. Thomas, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 515)
    - Hellman, Lillian(*), 1950-1956, n.d (Box 14, Folder 516)
    - Henderson, James, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 516)
    - Herrlinger, Robert(*), 1952-1956 (Box 14, Folder 517)
    - Hess, Walter R., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 517)
    - Hilles, Helen Train, (Mrs. Charles, Jr.), 1949-1955 (Box 14, Folder 518)
    - Hilles, Linda(*), 1951-1956 (Box 14, Folder 518)
    - Hintzsche, Erich(*), 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 519)
    - Hintzsche, Erich(*), 1950-1956 (Box 14, Folder 520)
    - Hippokrates-Verlag, 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 521)
    - Hippokrates-Verlag, 1952-1956 (Box 14, Folder 522)
    - Hirsch, Max, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Hochmuth, Grete Hertrand, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Hodgkinson, Ruth, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Hoenn, Karl, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Hofmann, M., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Holmyard, Eric John, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Holthusen, H., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Hou, Pao-chang, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Howald, Ernst(*), 1947-1955 (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Howard, Evelyn (Mrs. Michael), 1948-1954 (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Huber, Wilhelm, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Hübotter, Fritz, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Hülsmann, H. W., 1955, undated (Box 14, Folder 529)
    - Hume, Edward Hicks(*), 1947-1956 (Box 14, Folder 529)
    - Hunter, Harriot H., 1951-1953 (Box 14, Folder 530)
    - Hyman, Harold Thomas(*), 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 530)
    - Hyman, Harold Thomas(*), 1952-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 531)
    - I (Box 14, Folder 532)
    - Illing, Wolfram, 1951-1956 (Box 14, Folder 533)
    - Isenburg, Roberto, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 533)
    - Isis, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 534)
    - Iversen, Erik, 1948-1949 (Box 14, Folder 534)
    - Kaech, René, 1947-1956 (Box 14, Folder 535)
    - Jacob, Gerhard, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Jocobi, ____, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Jakob, Hans, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Janis, Lee
      See: box 7, folder 272
    - Janot, Maurice M., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Jantsch, Marlene, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Jarcho, Saul, 1952, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Jena, University of, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Jensen, Wu An (Mrs,), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Jörimann, Julius R., 1952-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - Johns Hopkins Press, 1947-1956 (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - Joint Distribution Committee
    - Jokl, Alexander(*), 1950-1953 (Box 14, Folder 541-542)
    - Jokl, Alexander(*), 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - Jokl, Ernst, 1948-1955 (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - Jonckheere, F., 1952, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 544)
    - Joris, Roger, 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 544)
    - Journal of World History (*), 1953-1954. (Box 15, Folder 545)
    - Juhn, B., 1953, undated (Box 15, Folder 546)
    - Jung, ____, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 546)
    - Ka-Kl (Box 15, Folder 547)
    - Ko-Ku (Box 15, Folder 548)
    - Kazakévich, Vladimir(*), 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 549)
    - Kahn, Eugen(*), 1948-1955, undated (Box 15, Folder 549)
    - Kalima, Tauno, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 550)
    - Kantor, Jacob Robert, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 550)
    - Kapadia, A. R., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 551)
    - Kapferer, Richard, 1951-1953 (Box 15, Folder 551)
    - Karcher, Johannes(*), 1950-1956 (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Kark, Sidney L., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Kartagener, Manes, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Katner, William(*), 1949-1956 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Katsch, Gerhardt, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Katz, A. (Mrs.), 1951 (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Kaufmann, Fritz, 1951-1955 (Box 15, Folder 555)
    - López Sánchez, José, 1949-1956 (Box 15, Folder 555)
    - Keller, J., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 556)
    - Kelman, Harold, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 556)
    - Kershaw, John, 1952-1956 (Box 15, Folder 557)
    - Kershaw, Pat (Mrs. John), 1952-1955 (Box 15, Folder 557)
    - Kessel, Lipmann(*), 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 557)
    - Kibre, Pearl (Mrs. Jeff), 1950-1951, n.d (Box 15, Folder 558)
    - Kingsbury, John Adams(*), 1948-1952 (Box 15, Folder 558)
    - Kingsbury, John Adams(*), 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 559)
    - Kingsbury, Mabel (Mrs. John), 1952, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 560)
    - Kisskalt, Karl, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 560)
    - Klaesi, Jakob, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 561)
    - Klein, Marianne, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 561)
    - Koch, Eugen, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 562)
    - Koch, Maria (Mrs. Richard), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 562)
    - Koch, Richard(*), 1947-1949, undated (Box 15, Folder 563)
      See also: box 8, folder 312
    - Koelhing, Martin Huldrych, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 564)
    - Rolle, Kurt(*), 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 564)
    - Kontzias, Helen, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 565)
    - Korbuly, George, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 565)
    - Korrodi, Eduard, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 566)
    - Koudelka, Janet Brock (Mrs. Carl)(*), 1947-1956 (Box 15, Folder 566)
    - Krantz, John C., Jr., 1949-1953 (Box 15, Folder 567)
    - Kraushaar, Otto F., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 567)
    - Krømer, Susanne Dybwad, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 568)
    - Krumbhaar, Edward Bell, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 568)
    - Krupp, Christian G., 1949 (Box 15, Folder 569)
    - Kruta, Vladislav, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 569)
    - Künstler, Margareta, 1948-1956 (Box 15, Folder 570)
    - Kulenkampff, ____, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 570)
    - Kym, Otto, 1950, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 571)
    - La (Box 15, Folder 572)
    - Le (Box 15, Folder 573)
    - Li-Lu (Box 15, Folder 574)
    - LaCava, Angelo Francesco, 1948-1954 (Box 15, Folder 575)
    - Lachman, Ernest, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 575)
    - Lachmann, Heinz, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 576)
    - Ladimer, Irving, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 576)
    - LaFia, David J., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 577)
    - Lain Entralgo, Pedro, 1946-1956 (Box 15, Folder 577)
    - Landsberg, Eva, 1948-1952 (Box 15, Folder 577)
    - Lange, Irene Zygoures (Mrs. Joachim)(*), 1947-1956 (Box 15, Folder 578)
    - Lange, Joachim, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 578)
    - Lange, Sophie (daughter of Irene and Joachim), 1948 (Box 15, Folder 579)
    - Langford-Rae, Elise M., 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 579)
    - Larkey, Geraldine (Mrs. Sanford V.) [to Emmy Sigerist], 1949 (Box 16, Folder 580)
    - Larkey, Sanford V., 1948-1954 (Box 16, Folder 580)
    - Lastres, Juan B., 1948-1954 (Box 16, Folder 580)
    - Laszlo, Henry de, 1952, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 581)
    - Latronico, Nicola, 1948-1953 (Box 16, Folder 581)
    - Lattimore, Owen, 1952-1955 (Box 16, Folder 582)
    - Lavoott, Rose, 1947, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 582)
    - Lawrence & Wishart, Ltd., 1950, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 583)
    - Lazaron, Hilda R., (Mrs. Morris)
      See: box 16, folder 583
    - Lazaron, Morris S.(*), 1947-1956 (Box 16, Folder 583)
    - Lazarus, Paul(*), 1948-1954 (Box 16, Folder 584)
    - Leake, Chauncey D.(*), 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 584)
    - Leake, Chauncey D.(*), 1950-1955 (Box 16, Folder 585)
    - Leaman, William G., 1948-1956 (Box 16, Folder 586)
    - LeFanu, William Richard, 1948-1952 (Box 16, Folder 586)
    - Leff, Samuel, 1950-1956 (Box 16, Folder 587)
    - Leff, Vera (Mrs. Samuel), 1954, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 587)
    - Lehmann, Hermann, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 588)
    - Leibowitz, Joshua O.(*), 1950-1956 (Box 16, Folder 588)
    - Leikind, Morris(*), 1948-1954 (Box 16, Folder 589)
    - Leisinger, H., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 589)
    - Leisten, Günther, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 590)
    - Lendi, J. U., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 590)
    - Lesky, Albin, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 591)
    - Lesky, Erna (Mrs.Albin), 1951-1956, undated (Box 16, Folder 591)
    - Leslie, Robert L.(*), 1947-1948 April-Dec, 1948-1956 (Box 16, Folder 592-595)
    - Levy, Doris Ruth Berlowitz, (Mrs. David)(*), 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 596)
    - Levy, Elsbeth(*), 1948-1956 (Box 16, Folder 597)
    - Licht, Sidney(*), 1950-1956 (Box 16, Folder 598)
    - Lichtenthaeler, Charles(*), 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 599)
    - Liebscher, Hellmuth, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 600)
    - Lier, Reinhard A. T(*), 1947-1950 (Box 16, Folder 600)
    - Lier, Reinhard A. T., 1951-1954 (Box 16, Folder 601)
    - Lindau, Theresa W. (Mrs. J. W.), 1948 (Box 16, Folder 602)
    - Lion, Gloria (Mrs. Albert), 1952-1953, undated (Box 16, Folder 602)
    - Lockwood, Dean P., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 603)
    - Löffler, Wilhelm, 1947-1951 (Box 16, Folder 603)
    - Löwenthal, Zdenko(*), 1951-1956, undated (Box 16, Folder 604-605)
    - London, University of, (miscellaneous)(*), 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 606)
      See also: box 17, folder 621
    - London, University of, London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine(*), 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 606)
    - Long, Esmond R.(*), 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 607)
    - Martí-Ibáñez, Félix, 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 608)
    - Lorenz, Helmut-Johannes, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 608)
    - Lossen, Heinz, 1953, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 609)
    - Louis, V., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 609)
    - Lowenthal, Max, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 610)
    - Lucia, Salvatore Pablo ("Sally"), 1948-1951, undated (Box 16, Folder 610)
    - Ludwig, Emil, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 611)
    - Ludwig, Gordon (son of Emil), 1947-1953 (Box 16, Folder 611)
    - Lüscher, Marie-Louise ("Bummi"), 1948-1951, undated (Box 16, Folder 612)
    - Lukács, Clara Briill (Mrs. Koloman), 1951 (Box 16, Folder 612)
    - Ma-Me (Box 17, Folder 613)
    - Mi-Mu (Box 17, Folder 614)
    - McClennan, Walter S., 1950, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 615)
    - McClure, Roy D., 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 615)
    - McCurdy, Robin, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 616)
    - McDaniel, Walter B., III, 1947-1956, n.d (Box 17, Folder 616)
    - McDonald, Donald, 1947-1952 (Box 17, Folder 617)
    - McGrath, Earl James, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 617)
    - McHenry, Lawrence C.(*), 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 618)
    - McKee, Thistle (Mrs. Toscan), 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 618)
    - Mackenzie, Cosmo, 1948-1952 (Box 17, Folder 619)
    - Mackenzie, Julia (Mrs. Cosmo), 1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 619)
    - MacKinney, Loren C., 1951-1956 (Box 17, Folder 620)
    - Mackintosh, James M.(*), 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 621)
      See also: box 16, folder 606
    - Mackintosh, James M.(*), 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 622)
    - MacLean, Basil Clarendon, 1948-1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 623)
    - MacLean, Hugh, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 623)
    - McPherson, Angus, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 624)
    - Maeder, A., 1951, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 624)
    - Magnus-Levy, Adolph, 1947-1952 (Box 17, Folder 625)
    - Major, Ralph H.(*), 1947-1955 (Box 17, Folder 625)
    - Makover, Henry B., 1948-1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 626)
    - Malik, Nur M., 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 626)
    - Mallwitz, A., 1953 (Box 17, Folder 627)
    - Malmberg, Carl, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 627)
    - Manchester, University of, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 628)
    - Mancke, R., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 628)
    - Mani, Nikolaus(*), 1950-1954, undated (Box 17, Folder 629)
    - Marbury, Margarita Lüttichau,(Mrs, William B.), 1947-1955 (Box 17, Folder 629)
    - Marcusson, Erwin, 1951-1954 (Box 17, Folder 630)
    - Margetts, Edward L., 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 630)
    - Marthinsen, Arne, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 631)
    - Martí-Ibáñez, Félix, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 631)
    - Poffet, Cécile (Mrs.), 1955-1956, undated (Box 17, Folder 632-633)
    - Martin, Joseph J., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 634)
    - Martínez Durán, Carlos, 1952-1956 (Box 17, Folder 634)
    - Marzell, Heinrich, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 635)
    - Matoušek, Miloslav(*), 1948-1956 (Box 17, Folder 635)
    - Matthias, L., 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - May, Hellmut, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Mayer, A., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Mayer, Claudius Frank, 1949, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - Mayer, Henry, 1954, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - MD Publications, Inc.
      See: box 17, folder 631
    - Medizinische Gesellschaft Basel, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Mehta, Pranjivan M.(*), 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Mehta, Pranjivan M.(*), 1952-1955 (Box 17, Folder 639)
    - Meng, Heinrich(*), 1948-1955 (Box 17, Folder 640)
    - Menninger, Karl A., 1949-1956 (Box 17, Folder 641)
    - Merke, Franz, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 641)
    - Metzner (Alfred) Verlag, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 642)
    - Meuli, ____, 1952, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 642)
    - Meyer, Adolf(*), 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 643)
    - Meyer, Agnes E. (Mrs. Eugene), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 644)
    - Meyer, E. F., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 644)
    - Meyer, Hannes, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 645)
    - Meyer, O., 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 645)
    - Michaud, Louis(*), 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 646)
    - Micheloni, Placido, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 647)
    - Miller, Benjamin Frank(*), 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 647)
    - Miller, Benjamin Frank(*), 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 648)
    - Miller, Genevieve, 1948-1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 649)
      See also: box 27, folder 924 See also: box 7, folder 271
    - Miller, Genevieve W. (Mrs. Charles, mother of Genevieve Miller), 1948, undated (Box 18, Folder 649)
    - Miller, Paul R., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 650)
    - Mills, J. G., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 650)
    - Milt, Bernhard(*), 1947-1956, undated (Box 18, Folder 651-656)
    - Minakami, Shigeki, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 657)
    - Miotto, Antonio, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 657)
    - Mitscherlich, Alexander, 1948, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 658)
    - Moericke, O., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 658)
    - Møller-Christensen, Vilhelm, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 659)
    - Molomut, Norman, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 659)
    - Monheimer, B. M.(*), 1949-1954, undated (Box 18, Folder 660)
    - Montagu, Ashley, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 661)
    - Monthly Review, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 661)
    - Moore, James, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 662)
    - Moorman, Lewis J., 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 662)
    - Moorman, Mary C. (Mrs. Lewis), 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 663)
    - Mooser, Hermann(*), 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 663)
    - Morris, J. N. (*), 1948-1952 (Box 18, Folder 664)
    - Mortensen, Vagn, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 664)
    - Moss, Joy(*), 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 665)
    - Mott, Frederick D., 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 665)
    - Mudaliar, A. Lakshmanaswami, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 666)
    - Mudd, Stuart, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 666)
    - Müller, Carl, 1951-1955 (Box 18, Folder 667)
    - Müller, Reinhold F. G., 1949-1955 (Box 18, Folder 668)
    - Münster, Ladislao(*), 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 669)
    - Muralt, Alexander L. von, 1948-1952 (Box 18, Folder 669)
    - Na-Ni (Box 18, Folder 670)
    - No-Ny (Box 18, Folder 671)
    - Nabarro, David, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 672)
    - Naef, Maria, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 672)
    - Nager, F. R., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 673)
    - Nardi, Michele Giuseppe, 1948, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 673)
    - National Research Council, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 674)
    - Neghme R., Amador, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 674)
    - Neubauer, R., 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 675)
    - Neuburger, Elise Reichenbach (Mrs. Arthur), 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 675)
    - Neuburger, Friedrich (son of Max), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 676)
    - Neuburger, Max, 1948, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 676)
    - Neue Zürcher Zeitung, 1948-1955, undated (Box 18, Folder 677)
    - Neumann, Rudolf, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 677)
    - Niles, Emory H., 1949 (Box 18, Folder 678)
    - Norpoth, Leo(*), 1948-1956 (Box 18, Folder 678)
    - Nothstein, Tegualda Ponce (Mrs. Alfred)
      See: box 19, folder 711
    - Nuffield Foundation, 1950-1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 679)
    - O (Box 18, Folder 680)
    - O'Donoghue, Patricia, 1951-1956 (Box 18, Folder 681)
    - Oeschger, Johannes, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 681)
    - Oettli, Theodor(*), 1949-1955 (Box 18, Folder 682)
    - Olschki (Leo S.) Editore(*), 1949-1956 (Box 18, Folder 682)
    - Olschki, Leonardo, 1951-1953 (Box 18, Folder 683)
    - O'Malley, Charles Donald, 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 683)
    - Optical Service, Inc., 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 684)
    - Ossendorf, Karel, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 684)
    - Oxford University Press(*), 1947-1948, 1949 January-Aug, 1949 October-Dec, 1950-1956 (Box 19, Folder 685-690)
    - P (Box 19, Folder 691)
    - Pachter, Henry M., 1951, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 692)
    - Pagel, Walter(*), 1947-1956 (Box 19, Folder 692)
    - Painter, Nivea (Mrs. Sidney), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 693)
    - Pannekoek, J. H., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 693)
    - Papaspyros, N. S., 1951-1954 (Box 19, Folder 694)
    - Paradise, Jack Leon(*), 1947-1956 (Box 19, Folder 694)
    - Paramore, R. H., 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 695)
    - Parisot, ____, undated (Box 19, Folder 695)
    - Park, Edwards A., 1948-1952 (Box 19, Folder 696)
    - Parsons, C. James F., 1947 (Box 19, Folder 696)
    - Pascua, M., 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 697)
    - Patel, Kanjibhai H., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 697)
    - Paz-Soldán, Carlos Enrique, 1949-1956 (Box 19, Folder 698)
    - Pazzini, Adalberto, 1949-1956 (Box 19, Folder 698)
    - Pedotti, Fausto, 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 699)
    - Pellegrini, Francesco, 1950-1955 (Box 19, Folder 699)
    - Peller, Sigismund, 1949-1954, undated (Box 19, Folder 700)
    - Pelseneer, Jean(*), 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 700)
    - Pelseneer, Jean(*), 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 701)
    - Penfield, Wilder, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 701)
    - Pepys, Jack, 1949-1956 (Box 19, Folder 702)
    - Pepys, Rhoda (Mrs. Jack), 1951-1954 (Box 19, Folder 702)
    - Perret, Louis, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 703)
    - Perry, Isabella H. ("Bell"), 1946-1955, undated (Box 19, Folder 703)
    - Pessl, Yella, 1947-1952 (Box 19, Folder 704)
    - Pestalozzi Foundation of America(*), 1947-1950 (Box 19, Folder 704)
    - Pestalozzi Foundation of America(*), 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 705)
    - Peters, Hannah, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 706)
    - Peters, John Punnett, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 706)
    - Peyer, Bernhard, 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 707)
    - Peyer, Hildegard (Mrs. Bernhard), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 707)
    - Physicians Forum(*), 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 708)
    - Piccini, Sergio, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 708)
    - Pijoan, Joseph, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 709)
    - Pijoan, Michel (son of Joseph), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 709)
    - Piotti, Achille, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 710)
    - Sand, René, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 710)
    - Poliakoff, Augusta, 1948-1953, undated (Box 19, Folder 711)
    - Ponce, Tegualda, (Mrs. Alfred Nothstein)(*), 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 711)
    - Poynter, Frederick N. L., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 712)
      See also: box 25, folder 888
    - Premuda, Loris(*), 1949-1956, undated (Box 19, Folder 712)
    - Price, Nettie, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 713)
    - Prigal, Esther (Mrs. Samuel J.), 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 713)
    - Prigal, Samuel J., 1951-1955 (Box 19, Folder 714)
    - Progressive Citizens of America, Science Division, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 714)
    - Proskauer, Curt, 1951-1956, undated (Box 19, Folder 715)
    - Provident Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1947-1958 (Box 19, Folder 716)
    - Quecke, Kurt, 1950-1955 (Box 19, Folder 716)
    - Ra-Re (Box 20, Folder 717)
    - Ri (Box 20, Folder 718)
    - Ro-Ru (Box 20, Folder 719)
    - Rabson, S. M.(*), 1953-1955 (Box 20, Folder 720)
    - Radbill, Samuel X., 1950-1956 (Box 20, Folder 721)
    - Radcliffe, Walter, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 721)
    - Raddin, Joseph B., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 722)
    - Radin, Doris (Mrs. Paul), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 722)
    - Radin, Paul, 1953-1956 (Box 20, Folder 723)
    - Rahman, ____, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 723)
    - Raina, B. L., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 724)
    - Raja, K. C. K. E., 1947-1950 (Box 20, Folder 724)
    - Ranganathan, S. R., 1951-1952 (Box 20, Folder 725)
    - Rath, Gernot(*), 1951-1956 (Box 20, Folder 725)
    - Rathinoff, Enrique, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 726)
    - Reddy, D. V. Subba(*), 1947-1951 (Box 20, Folder 726)
    - Reddy, D. V. Subba(*), 1952-1956 (Box 20, Folder 727)
    - Reichner, Herbert, 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 727)
    - Reucker, Karl(*), 1947-1956 (Box 20, Folder 728-732)
    - Reynolds, Frank W., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 733)
    - Richmond, Phyllis (Mrs. James Hugh)
      See: box 7, folder 270
    - Richter, Ida (Mrs. Robert), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 733)
    - Richter, Robert, 1947-1953, undated (Box 20, Folder 734)
    - Rieppel, Franz Wolfgang, 1952, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 734)
    - Ris, Hania Wislicka (Mrs. Hans), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 735)
    - Ritchie, William A., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 735)
    - Robinson, David M., 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 736)
    - Robinson, G. Canby, 1950, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 736)
    - Robinson, Richard, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 737)
    - Roemer, Milton I.(*), 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 738)
    - Roemer, Milton I.(*), 1949-1956 (Box 20, Folder 739-742)
    - Roemer, Ruth (Mrs. Milton I.), 1950-1952 (Box 20, Folder 743)
    - Röthlisberger, Johanna (Mrs. Paul), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 743)
    - Röthlisberger, Paul, 1947-1951 (Box 20, Folder 744)
    - Röthlisberger, Paul, 1952-1956. undated (Box 20, Folder 745-746)
    - Rogers, Frank B., 1953, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 747)
    - Rosen, George(*), 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 747)
    - Rosen, George(*), 1949-1952 (Box 21, Folder 748-749)
    - Rosen, George(*), 1953-1956, undated (Box 21, Folder 750)
    - Rosen, Victor II., 1948 (Box 21, Folder 751)
    - Rosenfeld, Leonard S.(*), 1948-1956 (Box 21, Folder 751)
    - Row, D. Naranaya, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 752)
    - Royal College of Physicians(*), 1951-1957 (Box 21, Folder 752)
    - Royal Society of Medicine(*), 1948-1955 (Box 21, Folder 753)
    - Ruhman, Walter, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 753)
    - Ruiz Moreno, Anibal, 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 754)
    - Ruoss, Erhard, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 754)
    - Rushmore, Stephen, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 755)
    - Ruyter, L. de, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 755)
    - Ryle, John A., 1948-1950, n.d (Box 21, Folder 756)
    - Sa (Box 21, Folder 757)
    - Sc (Box 21, Folder 758)
    - Se-So (Box 21, Folder 759)
    - Sp-Stei (Box 21, Folder 760)
    - Stem-Sz (Box 21, Folder 761)
    - Sallenbach, Lily Keller (Mrs.)(*), 1951-1956 (Box 21, Folder 762)
    - Salzmann Charles, 1950-1956 (Box 21, Folder 763)
    - Bickel, André [nephew], 1947-1951 (Box 21, Folder 764)
    - Sandoz A. G., 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 765)
    - Sarton, George(*), 1947-1955 (Box 21, Folder 765)
    - Sarton, Mabel (Mrs. George), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 766)
    - Sarton, May, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 766)
    - Saunders, John B. deC. M., 1949, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 767)
    - Saussure, Raymond de(*), 1948-1956 (Box 21, Folder 767)
    - Scarlett, Earle P., 1953, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 768)
    - Schadewaldt, Hans, 1951-1956 (Box 21, Folder 768)
    - Schaffner, Bertram, 1953, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 769)
    - Scheu, Tamara (Mrs, Volker), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 769)
    - Scheu, Volker(*), 1947-1955 (Box 21, Folder 770)
    - Schiaffino, Rafael(*), 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 770)
    - Schinz, Anni, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 771)
    - Schinz, Ginevra (Mrs. Hans R.)(*), 1948-1953 (Box 21, Folder 771)